<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE mrgmandoctype [
<!ENTITY mrgman_form_feed "&#10;">
]>
<sdf>
	<interfaceInformation id="1">
		<serviceName>NativeEBTSResponseService</serviceName>
		<version></version>
		<description>This service must be implemented by a CSA to accept a response from NGI.</description>
		<semanticModel>
			<type></type>
			<subject></subject>
			<intendedUsers>CJIS - NGI</intendedUsers>
			<references/>
		</semanticModel>
		<operation>
			<name>receiveResponse</name>
			<description>Allows NGI to submit a response to a CSA.</description>
			<inputDescription>NativeEBTSMessage element should contain a base-64 encoded native EBTS message, in accordance with EBTS.</inputDescription>
			<outputDescription>None. The output type is defined merely to support a request/response message pattern so that a SOAP fault can be thrown by a CSA to indicate an error in accepting an response from NGI.</outputDescription>
			<preconditions>Authorized Contributor must have network access to a CJIS interface agency, which has made
				agreements with CJIS and installed an interface to the CJIS data
				center.</preconditions>
			<effects>A response based upon a CSA's previously submitted request is accepted and processed by the CSA.</effects>
			<errors>If a CSA internal system error (such as a database is down) has occurred prior to the CSA system's ability to process a submitted NGI's request, a SOAP fault with the error condition encountered will need to be thrown on the "receiveResponse" operation. This indicates that the CSA system has not accepted the NGI's request to deliver a response to the CSA.</errors>
		</operation>
	</interfaceInformation>
	<securityInformation>
		<securityMechanism>This is implemented by the CSA. If there are any security mechanisms that a CSA implements for this operation, this must be coordinated with CJIS prior to using NGI services.</securityMechanism>
		<accessCriteriaAndRestrictions>
			<accessModel>User must access via a CJIS Systems Agency (CSA) in one of the 50 states, the District of Columbia, Puerto Rico, the Virgin Islands, Guam, or Canada; or via a federal criminal justice agency. Authorized Contributor must have network access to a CJIS interface agency, which has made agreements with CJIS and installed an interface to the CJSI data center.

CSA must also work with CJIS to register their response and unsolicited notification service endpoints prior to using NGI services. If a CSA has not completed this process, no responses will be delivered to the CSA.</accessModel>
			<restrictions>This is implemented by the CSA. NGI must be granted an authorization to access this service in order to deliver an NGI response.</restrictions>
		</accessCriteriaAndRestrictions>
		<informationSecurityMarking>
			<classification></classification>
			<classificationReason/>
			<derivedFrom/>
			<disseminationControls/>
			<ownerProducer/>
			<releasableTo/>
		</informationSecurityMarking>
	</securityInformation>
	<serviceLevelInformation>
		<serviceLevelSpecification id="1">
			<name>STANDARD</name>
			<cost></cost>
			<availability>This is implemented by the CSA.</availability>
			<capacity>This is implemented by the CSA.</capacity>
			<responseTime>This is implemented by the CSA.</responseTime>
			<scheduledDowntime></scheduledDowntime>
			<other></other>
		</serviceLevelSpecification>
		<networkRequirements>
			<bandwidth></bandwidth>
			<latency></latency>
			<jitter></jitter>
		</networkRequirements>
	</serviceLevelInformation>
	<implementationInformation>
		<consumerPattern>
			<name>Request/Response. 

A typical pattern is as follows:

1. A CSA initially submits a request and a NCN response is provided by NGI upon accepting the request. 

2. Upon completing a CSA's request, NGI will initiate another request/response with the CSA's implemented response service to receive the response for the previously submitted request.</name>
			<sampleCode/>
		</consumerPattern>
		<scheduleDate>
			<type>OPERATION</type>
			<description>CSA's must implement this service prior to submitting requests to NGI</description>
			<startDate></startDate>
			<endDate></endDate>
		</scheduleDate>
		<operationalReference>
			<name/>
			<description/>
			<reference/>
		</operationalReference>
		<versioningApproach>Versioning will be accomplished using a naming
			scheme based on date. The date version is applied to the services
			wsdls, xsds, and the endpoint.</versioningApproach>
	</implementationInformation>
	<pocInformation>
		<contact id="1">
			<type>APPROVER</type>
			<organization>CJIS</organization>
			<name>NGI Program Office</name>
			<address>
				<street>1000 Custer Hollow Road</street>
				<city>Clarksburg</city>
				<state>WV</state>
				<country>USA</country>
			</address>
			<email>EBTSSupport@ic.fbi.gov</email>
			<uri/>
			<phone>1-304-625-5590</phone>
		</contact>
	</pocInformation>
	<sapInformation>
		<serviceAccessPoint>
			<binding>SOAP_HTTP</binding>
			<port>port</port>
			<pocReference></pocReference>
			<supplementalInformation></supplementalInformation>
			<technicalDescriptionType>WSDL</technicalDescriptionType>
			<technicalDescription>NativeEBTSResponseService.wsdl</technicalDescription>
		</serviceAccessPoint>
	</sapInformation>
</sdf>